v4orkut.com 2015-05-16

# Privacy Policy - V4orkut.Com

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of V4orkut.

V4orkut will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on V4orkut.

V4orkut does not use affiliate links on the site and request that you notify us immediately if you come across any.

V4orkut uses Google Adsense to display advertisement and Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to V4orkut users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

V4orkut is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows V4orkut to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and V4orkut does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to V4orkut and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through V4orkut have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information, please email the founder, at _admin@V4orkut.com_
